{"data":[{"question":"What a _________ day it is!","a":"lovely","b":"dearly","c":"likely","d":"lively","answer":"1","explain":"- What a\/an + adj + ...!","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Dodge is ___ coach that all of the players like him.","a":"such good","b":"a such good","c":"so good a","d":"a so good","answer":"3","explain":"- so .... that","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"It is dark, but all of the employees are _________ in the office.","a":"already","b":"yet","c":"still","d":"also","answer":"3","explain":"-\u00a0Still: Not moving","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ should help ___.","a":"The strong, weak people","b":"Strong people, weak one","c":"The strong, the weak","d":"Strong, weak","answer":"3","explain":"- the + adj to talk about groups of people","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___, the worse I seem to be.","a":"Taking more of the medicine","b":"When I take more medicine","c":"The more medicine taken","d":"The more medicine I take","answer":"4","explain":"- the + adj -er .... the + adj -er","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The more the mechanic explained, ___ I understood.","a":"fewer","b":"the least","c":"the fewer","d":"the less","answer":"4","explain":"- the + adj -er .... the + adj -er","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Why did you ask Mike for help instead of Martin? He is ___ helpful than Martin.","a":"any more","b":"no more","c":"some more","d":"not more","answer":"4","explain":"- The comparative form of long adjective (helpful)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How blond your sister's skin is! \"It's ___ mine when I was at his age.\"","a":"no more blonder than","b":"no blonder than","c":"no blond as","d":"not blonder more than","answer":"2","explain":"- No + comparative form","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"From then on, Jason didn't see his best friend ___.","a":"no longer","b":"no more","c":"any long","d":"anymore","answer":"4","explain":"- anymore = any longer","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you be ___ to step this way, please?","a":"so kind","b":"too kind","c":"as kind as","d":"so kind as","answer":"4","explain":"- so + adj + as to","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}